<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Irina Parenko</title>
    <description>Digital Marketing Specialist</description>
    <link>https://www.linkedin.com/in/irinaparenko///</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/irinaparenko///feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:10:38 +1200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:10:38 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hi there!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Irina, I&#39;m entry-level professional with experience, skills, and knowledge in Digital Marketing. I&#39;ve recently graduated from Auckland University of Technology as a Bachelor of Business specializing in Marketing and Economics. Over last year I&#39;ve been working with a couple of IT companies that develop fascinating digital products in Agile environment for numerous markets around the world.

I&#39;ve got knowledge, skills, and experience in:  
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Market Research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Running Digital Marketing Campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Google AdWords &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Facilitation of Product demos for clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Sales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a fast-learner with great communication skills, passionate when it comes to Digital Marketing and Economics. I have an ability to work with others in unison, confident to work under pressure, as well as without supervision. Learning and adapting fast to rapidly changing conditions is my credo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In addition to the above I&#39;ve also got experience in: 
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; project management planning activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; resource planning and scheduling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; product development status reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; development team meetings facilitation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; communication with internal and external stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To summarise, I’m easy-going person and a great team-player. At work I&#39;m always focused on quality, efficiency, and given deadlines. I always plan in advance by prioritising tasks, defining scope, mitigating risks, and then executing required actions. It always leads me to achieve task completion in time with the desired quality. Multitasking is also not a problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the moment I&#39;m open for offers and looking for new opportunities. Do not hesitate to contact me in that regard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight:bold&quot;&gt; --- 
&lt;br /&gt;Kind Regards,
&lt;br /&gt;Irina Parenko&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 23:28:00 +1200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.linkedin.com/in/irinaparenko///2017/about/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.linkedin.com/in/irinaparenko///2017/about/</guid>
        
        <category>about</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
